Guide to the John Franklin Enders Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Laboratory Notebooks, 1947-1976; Series III; 14' (34 Boxes)
  - Lang, David J.: Volume IV: Bacteriology 206, Circa 1965 (Box 121, Folder 77)
  - Leas: Volume I, Circa 1960-1961 (Box 121, Folder 78)
  - Leas: Volume II, Circa 1961-1962 (Box 121, Folder 79)
  - Leas: Volume IV, Circa 1963 (Box 122, Folder 80)
  - McCarthy: Volume I, Circa 1964-1965 (Box 122, Folder 81)
  - Malherbe, Hubert: Volume I, Circa 1953-1954 (Box 122, Folder 82)
  - Medearis, Donald: Volume I, Circa 1956-1957 (Box 122, Folder 83)
  - Medearis, Donald: Volume II, Circa 1957-1958 (Box 123, Folder 84)
  - Medearis, Donald: Volume III, Circa 1958 (Box 123, Folder 85)
  - Melendez, Luis: Volume I, Circa 1955 (Box 123, Folder 86)
  - Melendez, Luis: Volume II, Circa 1955-1956 (Box 123, Folder 87)
  - Mills, John, Circa 1955-1956 (Box 124, Folder 88)
  - Milovanovic, M. V.: Volume I, 1955 July-1956 September (Box 124, Folder 89)
  - Milovanovic, M. V.: Volume II, Circa 1956-1957 (Box 124, Folder 90)
  - Mosley, James W.: Volume I, Circa 1959-1960 (Box 124, Folder 91)
  - Mosley, James W.: Volume II, Circa 1960 (Box 125, Folder 92)
  - Mosley, James W.: Volume III, Circa 1960-1961 (Box 125, Folder 93)
  - Mosley, James W.: Volume IV, Circa 1961 (Box 125, Folder 94)
  - Naficy, Kiarash: Volume I, Circa 1961-1962 (Box 125, Folder 95)
  - Naficy, Kiarash: Volume II, Circa 1962-1963 (Box 126, Folder 96)
  - Naficy, Kiarash: Volume III, Circa 1963 (Box 126, Folder 97)
  - Naficy, Kiarash: Myocarditis, undated (Box 126, Folder 98)
  - Naficy, Kiarash
    See also: box 119, folder 68
  - Nagata, Ikuya: Volume I, Circa 1960-1961 (Box 126, Folder 99)
  - Nagata, Ikuya: Volume II, Circa 1961 (Box 127, Folder 100)
  - Nagata, Ikuya: Volume III, Circa 1961 (Box 127, Folder 101)
  - Neff, John: Volume I, Circa 1966-1967 (Box 127, Folder 102)
  - Neff, John: Volume II, Ca. 1967 (Box 127, Folder 103)
  - Neff, John: Volume III, Circa 1967-1968 (Box 128, Folder 104)
  - Nesburn, Anthony B.: Volume I, Circa 1964-1966 (Box 128, Folder 105)
  - Nesburn, Anthony B.: Volume III, Circa 1965-1966 (Box 128, Folder 106)
  - Neva, Franklin A.: Volume I, Circa 1951-1953 (Box 128, Folder 107)
  - Neva, Franklin A.: Volume III, Circa 1952-1953 (Box 129, Folder 108)
  - Peebles, Thomas J., Circa 1953-1954 (Box 129, Folder 109)
  - Peres, Jose Noronha, Circa 1956 (Box 129, Folder 110)
  - Pons, Marcel W.: Volume I, Circa 1958-1959 (Box 129, Folder 111)
  - Pons, Marcel W.: Volume II, Circa 1960 (Box 130, Folder 112)
  - Robbins, Frederick C.: Volume I, Circa 1948-1949 (Box 130, Folder 113)
  - Robbins, Frederick C.: Volume II, Circa 1949-1950 (Box 130, Folder 114)
  - Robbins, Frederick C.: Volume III, Circa 1950 (Box 130, Folder 115)
  - Robbins, Frederick C.: Volume IV, Circa 1950-1951 (Box 131, Folder 116)
  - Robbins, Frederick C.: Volume V, Circa 1951-1952 (Box 131, Folder 117)
  - Rosenthal, Melvin S.: Volume I, Circa 1958-1960 (Box 131, Folder 118)
  - Rosenthal, Melvin S.: Volume II, Circa 1960 (Box 131, Folder 119)
  - Shein, Harvey M.: Volume I, Circa 1959-1960 (Box 132, Folder 120)
  - Shein, Harvey M.: Volume III, Circa 1961-1962 (Box 132, Folder 121)
  - Shein, Harvey M.: Volume IV, Circa 1962 (Box 132, Folder 122)
  - Shein, Harvey M., Circa 1960-1961 (Box 132, Folder 123)
  - Shein, Harvey M.: Tissue Book, Circa 1961 (Box 133, Folder 124)
  - Shein, Harvey M., undated (Box 133, Folder 125)
  - Shein, Harvey M., Circa 1962-1963 (Box 133, Folder 126)
  - Shope, Richard E.: Papilloma Data, Circa 1955 (Box 133, Folder 127)
  - Smith, John W.: Volume I, Circa 1961 (Box 134, Folder 128)
  - Svedmyr, Arne, Circa 1951-1952 (Box 134, Folder 129)
  - Vieuchange, Jean: Volume I, Circa 1955 (Box 134, Folder 130)
  - Vieuchange, Jean, Circa 1963-1964 (Box 134, Folder 131)
  - Warren, Joel: Volume I, Circa 1964 (Box 135, Folder 132)
  - Warren, Joel: Volume II, Circa 1964 (Box 135, Folder 133)